Provided by DragonHQD
Modify by Blue-Bird™
♪ Jane, you say it's all over ♪
♪ for you and me, girl ♪
♪ there's a time for love ♪
♪ and a time for
letting it be, baby ♪
♪ Jane, you're playing
a game called... ♪
Whoo!
♪ Making believe that
you just don't feel the same ♪
Yeah!
♪ Oh, Jane ♪
Whoo!
Mmm, mmm.
♪ Whoa, Jane,
you're playing a game ♪
♪ called hide-and-go-seek ♪
Whoo!
Mwah.
♪ Jane, you're playing
for fun... ♪
- Whoo!
You know
the first thing I thought
when I saw you?
I thought, "I want to make
a child with that person."
What if it's a her?
What would you call her?
Ragni, maybe.
Sorry?
Ragni.
Uh, let me think about
that for a second.
- Ragni.
- You hate it.
- Uh, boy's name?
- Texas.
You kidding me?
Texas is, like, a state,
you know? -I know.
There's about
three or four hours
till we reach the peak.
Ah, great.
Sweetie, can I just say
one last thing?
Then, I swear,
no more wedding talk.
- Of course.
- It's about the band.
But that is the one thing
you said I could handle myself,
and I've already made
my decision, Elsa.
Yeah, it's just that
I don't want
to use your brother's band.
- Why not?
- Honey...
He's super, super good.
- He works super hard.
- Yeah.
And-and he-he even takes
vocal lessons now.
Yeah, I know this.
I know this. It's just that,
um, well, Eric is no good.
I mean, he's, well,
terrible, actually.
His singing is like shit.
Hey. I mean, he has a nice b...
Olaf!
Olaf, I didn't mean to...
Oh, god.
Wait for me.
Why are you so sensitive?
Told you I could get us here.
It's beautiful.
Thank you. I love you.
Elsa.
- Look. Look.
- What is it? Hmm? Hmm?
- Look.
Quick, the camera.
Get the camera.
Oh, my, I've always wanted
to see a bear in real life.
First, humpbacks in Iceland,
and now this.
We have such good luck
in nature.
What do you see?
Hmm?
It's demented or something.
What?
Can I get the camera?
Give me the camera. -Yeah.
Demented?
I-I-I think we should leave it.
It's-it's something wrong
with it. Come on.
- Come on...
Ah!
Shh. Come on.
It's so cute.
Oh, there's nothing
to be afraid of, kristoffer.
I'm not afraid, Elsa.
Oh, sweetie, now, of course not.
Oh, fuck.
Don't panic.
What do we do?
"If it's black, fight back.
If it's brown, lay down."
But is it black or is it brown?
I mean, it looks brown to me.
We're in appalachia.
It's black.
- We have to fight it.
- How do you know?
You're not a bear expert.
Whatever you do, don't...
- Run! Where are we going?
- Oh-oh, no. Oh-oh, no.
- I said don't run! Stop! Stop!
- Uphill. Uphill.
Run!
- Where do we go?
- Run, Elsa! Run!
Oh, my god. Oh, my god!
- Run!
He's coming! Come on!
No! It's following...
Olaf! No!
God!
Help me!
- Come on! Come on!
Olaf!
This is drugs.
This is your brain on drugs.
It isn't glamorous
or cool or kid stuff.
The thrill can kill.
Smoking crack is like
putting a gun in your mouth...
And pulling the trigger.
Millions of dollars' worth of
cocaine dropped from the sky
early today onto a driveway
in Knoxville, Tennessee.
Kenley Jones reports tonight
it was found
on the body of a man
who fell to his death
when his parachute
failed to open.
The body of the heavily
armed parachutist was found
early this morning
by 85-year-old Fred Myers
and his neighbor, Ralph Johnson.
And you could see that
his main chute didn't open,
so I guess the loafers
was too much for him.
Police found more than
70 pounds of cocaine
wrapped in
football-size packages
in a duffel bag
the chutist was carrying.
Emergency chute deployed,
but didn't help much, I suppose.
Any narcotics found
with the plane wreckage?
Nothing.
Here's the I.D.
I know who that is.
Full name:
Andrew c. Thornton ii.
Man was out of his mind.
- What's the "c" stand for?
- Hmm?
You said "full name," but
you didn't say his full name.
Thornton was one of Syd
white's guys out of Missouri.
He's a known drug trafficker
with ties to Colombia.
Part of
the bluegrass conspiracy.
And there's more of this
out there.
They dumped it somewhere.
Hey, reba,
you have a dog, right?
Had.
Border collie. Barry.
Sorry for your loss.
Border collie, huh?
That's a cool dog.
Did he play fetch and stuff?
He loved fetch.
What?
Nothing. I just...
That's just awesome.
Damn it, Gabe.
Hi, daveed.
Uh, mind if I order first?
This won't take long.
Damn, I just bought these.
Hey, how's Gabe doing, anyway?
Did you hear about Thornton?
It's a tough way to go.
He only had 30 kilos on him.
Any idea where
we could find the rest?
Chattahoochee.
Georgia?
There's an area
called blood mountain.
When the plane's going down,
the pilots know
where to drop our load.
And then we just go and get it.
I don't need a bunch
of worried Colombians.
Now, I want you
to take Eddie with you.
Eddie's in mourning.
Joanie just died.
And he quit.
Joanie's the reason why he quit.
She's not here anymore.
The sooner he moves on,
the better.
Syd, I-I just don't...
Stop.
He won't even come
to get his goddamn son.
I am sick and tired
of watching my kid's kid.
Grandpa Syd, watch.
Yeah, that's great.
Got to go. Shift starts at 8:00.
Tomorrow's lunch is in
the fridge, and the chicken's...
Chicken's in the microwave.
Just hit "start."
Thought you were off tonight.
We talked about this, remember?
Me picking up some extra shifts?
You said you were okay with it.
I was okay with it
until I realized
why you want
those extra shifts...
So you could go and do overtime
with ray the pediatrician.
Gross, Dee Dee. Gross.
You know, he invited us
to go to Nashville
this weekend
to see his band play.
We were supposed to go paint
the waterfall this weekend.
I know, but it's gonna be fun.
We're gonna make
a whole weekend out of it.
It's Nashville.
He's a good guy, deirdra.
Just...
Give him a chance.
Please don't do that.
Do what?
You know what.
We'll paint the waterfall
another weekend, okay?
Close my door.
That's enough for today.
Wait, what?
Hey, Eddie.
They spelled her name wrong, daveed.
- It says "John."
- Oh.
- Says "John."
- Yeah.
- Her name is fucking Joan.
- Look, we...
- We could get it fixed.
- No.
I got to wait a week
for it to heal first.
I got seven more days of "John."
The chutist has been identified
as Andrew Thornton
of Paris, Kentucky.
- Wait, is that us?
- Hey.
Listen, Syd is worried
about you, all right?
Says you haven't seen Gabe
in weeks.
I'm so sad, man.
I'm so fucking sad.
Okay?
Can I get the, uh...
The penne, please?
Does it come with chicken,
or is it just, uh...
It's just plain.
I knew you'd be late.
It finally came in.
Check it out.
How many weeks' allowance
is that?
Like a thousand, but worth it.
- Can I use the toilet?
- Uh, no.
My mom is gonna be home soon.
And we got to go if we want
to get to the falls by lunch.
Why by lunch?
The light, Henry.
But I got to go pee.
Go outside.
Why do I skip school with you?
You're bossier than
the teachers.
Now, the adoption people...
I'm not sure who I talked to
over there...
Told me I was supposed to be
getting me a lab.
A fun one, a...
A man's-best-friend type.
I don't know
if there was an error,
because the one I got
is just kind of...
Bob?
- I don't know,
just kind of fancy.
Bob, captain says
it's time to go. -Got it.
Hey, look, I'm gonna
have to call you back.
Hey, reba.
You got plans for tonight?
Uh, Bob, you're a nice guy.
- I just don't...
- Mind looking after rosette?
- Oh.
- I have to go to Georgia
for the Thornton case,
and you said
you were good at dogs.
I said I had a dog.
You don't have jurisdiction
in Georgia.
A trucker overheard
a couple of guys
talking at a bar last night.
- I'll tell you in the car.
- No, no, no.
Pretty sure they're Syd's guys.
Oh, come on. You got to be
sort of good with them.
I only had her for a day.
Please?
Uh, I don't know if I could
trust anyone else around here.
Just go.
We'll be fine.
Thanks.
Can't believe
I left the backpack.
I can. I know the way.
School's gonna call, you know.
You know what? Let 'em.
And your mom's gonna be pissed.
So's your dad.
He doesn't care if I play hooky.
For a girl who likes
to be left alone,
you do a lot of shit
for attention.
Look, I'm not
ditching for attention.
I just want to paint
the waterfall.
Admit it.
You want her to find out
and worry about you.
- Jesus! Fuck!
Coral, it's sari.
Is Dee Dee over there?
School just called.
No.
Yeah, well, can you just
put Elliot on?
Yes, well, his daughter
just ditched school,
so can you please
just put him on?
Every time I call,
he's in the bathroom.
What the hell is wrong with him?
Never mind.
♪ A love song of the waterfall ♪
♪ I hear through
virgin timbertop... ♪
50 cents.
I'm not gonna see
that wrapper outside
- on the ground, now, am I?
- No, ma'am.
You one of those kids
caused me a bunch of shit?
- What?
- Empty your pockets.
Vest pocket. Come on.
Is that perfume?
That's none of your business.
Well, it smells really nice.
Yeah, well, it's European.
Oh.
Yeah, I'm expecting someone
in a minute.
Is it too much?
Not at all.
Smells expensive.
Well, it is.
You want a sucker?
Sure.
I like the green one.
This is a red one.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Uh-huh.
Oh, shit. He's here.
Am I in the right place?
Oh! Right.
Told you it was big.
Oh, it's big.
What's that smell?
It's European.
Someone been smoking?
Um, he was.
- Can you believe it?
- What?
You know,
cigarettes kill people.
- Yeah, but...
- And animals.
Forest fires are the number one
cause of death for wildlife.
Yeah, and y-you should be
educating yourself
instead of endangering
the entire ecosystem.
Just get out of here.
- Get out.
Unbelievable.
You got a dusty beaver here, ranger.
Yeah, well, I'm working on that.
Hey, Henry!
It looks like the deer
on this sign are doing it!
Hold on.
Seriously, what the hell
are you even doing?
Marking our territory.
Ugh! Don't shit out here!
I'm not shitting.
Hey. Did your mom pack
double lunch for school again?
My dad didn't have a chance
to make any.
Hey, Henry.
Check it out.
It's drugs, I think.
It's drugs?
Remember that guy from assembly?
He showed us pictures of stuff
that looked just like this.
Yeah. The guy from Vietnam
with no legs.
No.
This is definitely cocaine.
Yeah. Of course.
I'm just not used to
seeing it like that.
You know, it's usually
more powdery on the streets.
When have you seen cocaine
on the streets?
When I do it.
Oh, yeah?
With who?
With faulk.
After church.
Faulk does not do cocaine
after church.
Are you friends with faulk?
No. He's a pervert.
Then you wouldn't know.
Liar.
You're just mad
you're never invited.
I don't care I'm not invited.
Sounds like you care.
Do some, then.
What?
You've done it before.
You can do it again.
Well, uh, we're exercising,
though. Shooting and stuff.
I mean, I can't do cocaine
while shooting and exercising.
That wouldn't be good.
Fine.
Knife me.
Okay, so how do I do it?
You eat it.
How much?
Like a tablespoon's worth.
Oh!
- Son of a bitch!
Oh, what the hell?
- Rookie.
You do it, then.
Ugh.
- Ah, shit!
What the hell?
This isn't as good
as the shit I normally do.
Ugh!
How much do you think
this stuff is worth?
Let's sell drugs together.
Yeah, we could sell them on
the street like you and faulk.
There's more.
Ow.
Something got into it.
A deer, maybe.
Could you imagine that?
Deer on cocaine?
It'd be like this.
Yeah, it'd be, like,
going into trees like... bang!
- Bang!
- Yep, and then it'd get stuck.
Yeah, and then it'd be so sad.
Hey, Dee Dee. Do you think
my dad has ever done cocaine?
Your dad has definitely
done cocaine.
My throat's really runny.
Stop that.
Did it do the cocaine?
Don't move a muscle.
Listen to me.
You were supposed to grab Eddie,
not run your mouth.
Now we have trouble.
You understand? -Got it.
- I'll take care of it.
Gabe, knock that off. Gabe.
Grandpa Syd!
Gabe, driving me nuts.
Little...
Fuck.
♪ Is on the wings of love ♪
♪ on the wings of love ♪
♪ only the two of us ♪
♪ together flying high ♪
♪ flying high
up on the wings of love... ♪
Joan loved this song.
She said he sang with the soul
of a thousand-year-old man.
Um, Eddie, listen.
Uh, when joanie died,
I'm sorry I didn't, you know...
It's fine.
No, I could've did more.
I should've been there.
I didn't need you there.
I don't hang out
with drug dealers anymore.
It's against my constitution.
I'm more than a drug dealer.
- No, you're not.
- Come on, Eddie.
We're friends, right?
No.
Fine.
I think he's happy she's dead.
He's not happy she died.
Blamed her for me leaving
the family business,
if we can call it that.
Sometimes...
- I wonder if he did it to her.
- What?
No, joanie died of cancer.
I know.
Maybe he gave her the cancer.
You can't give no one cancer.
Yes, you can. With stress.
Stop protecting him.
You know what?
Maybe I should turn this off.
No!
♪ Running free, traveling ♪
♪ on the wings of love ♪
Okay.
♪ On the wings of love,
up and above... ♪
Okay, so we start...
- Did you notice my nails?
- Those are beautiful.
- Thank you. We start...
- Excuse me. Is the ranger in?
I'm wearing the stuff.
Oh. Did either of you
see a girl,
13, come through here?
My daughter...
You lost your daughter
in the park.
Well, she came here on her own,
heading to the waterfall.
Yeah. Hikers under 16 must be
accompanied by an adult.
Well, I didn't know
she was coming here.
You know, we get
a lot of runaways,
bad apples,
youngsters who aren't too happy
with the way things are at home.
She's not a runaway.
She just came to paint the...
Can someone just please point me
in the direction
of blood mountain?
This is blood mountain.
- Sorry. I-I'm Peter.
Oh.
This is Peter,
wildlife inspection rep.
We're about to head up there ourselves.
Oh. Do you mind if I tag along?
Now, Peter,
the wildlife inspection
is a very important process.
We wouldn't want you distracted
by our little
damsel in distress here.
Nothing can distract me
from making sure
the entire biological community
is safe for all our friends.
Friends?
- He means animals.
- I don't like that word.
He doesn't like
to call them animals.
Well, I won't be a burden.
I'll get my hat.
Okay.
Shoes okay for hiking?
Oh, yeah.
I-I think I'll be okay.
I have on boots.
- Yep.
Come on, Eddie.
I'm done playing this game.
You-you wanted...
You were the one
who wanted to play this.
You still have
three more questions.
Listen.
What?
I'm tired of playing
this fucking game.
No, you're not.
You just don't want to lose.
I'm-a go in here
and take a piss, all right?
I didn't know
rangers carried guns.
Park rangers are peace officers.
Which means we can shoot people.
Forest is a dangerous place.
That gang of pubes
are dangerous.
"Gang of pubes"?
Teens. Delinquents.
They've been attacking hikers.
They hurt anyone?
They cut them with a knife.
Call themselves the doochamps.
Watch your back.
Pop-art punks
pop up out of nowhere.
Out of nowhere.
Fuck is this?
He's afraid, buds.
Empty your pockets.
No.
Empty your pockets, please.
Since you asked so nicely.
You think this is a joke?
I do.
Get him, buds.
I'm shaking
a fucking knife, man. Come on.
Just stab him. -Come on, man.
It's a fucking knife!
- Go on!
Oh!
Come on, rocky. Come on, rocky.
- Come on, rocky.
- Ah! Banzai!
Give me this fucking board!
You're going down, man!
Submit! Submit!
What the...
Hold this!
Aah! Fucking skateboard!
Oh, my.
The fuck is wrong with y'all?!
Shit!
I love this road.
Ah, love it up there.
So, wait, where is it
that you wanted to go again?
What? The falls.
The secret falls. Right, well,
we can go up this way
- or take the loop.
I love the loop.
Well, you can see
the top of the...
This is a more direct...
All right. We're going this way.
Well, crap.
Told you she shouldn't
have come with us.
Just distracting you completely.
She can hear you.
I wanted to get up
to see the sunset.
- What's taking you so long?
What'd you do?
Please tell me
you found them like this.
They attacked me.
Are they dead?
Well, one might be.
The-the one that stabbed me
might be dead.
Jesus chr... they're kids.
I loved this fucking Jersey, man.
Okay, they're fine.
Thank god.
No fucking way.
Daveed?
What happened?
Hey.
- Wake up.
Where'd you find this?
Whoa.
Where is this energy
coming from, bud?
You tried to fucking kill me.
You got a foul mouth there, bud.
I tell him that all the time.
Where did you find this?
Up on the mountain.
Where's the rest of it?
I don't know.
Listen, I just took out
the three of you in 15 seconds.
What do you think I'll do
to just you
when you're already
on the floor?
Okay. Okay.
We stashed it under a gazebo.
Going back for it later tonight.
A gazebo?
It's a pavilion-type structure.
I know what the fuck
a gazebo is.
I didn't.
Are my buds dead?
- Show us where.
- Oh, god.
You know,
i-I'm feeling kind of tired.
I think I should rest.
Okay. Want a dirt nap?
Eddie, go get the gun.
It's in the glove.
I prefer we left guns
out of this.
Yeah. Same.
And I would prefer
not to be stabbed.
So, Eddie, please go get
the fucking gun.
Okay.
All right, all right.
All right, I'm coming.
Relax.
It's getting real cold out.
Let's go.
So, where you guys from?
Shut up. Keep walking.
Gonna be a long hike
if we can't talk to each other.
It better not be a long hike.
Friend's
pretty serious, ain't he?
Well, I don't think
he's too happy
after getting stabbed
in the shoulder.
Well, it wasn't me.
Eh, I don't blame him, though.
Getting stabbed sucks.
Hey, shut the fuck up.
♪ Well, you're too hot ta trot,
now, baby ♪
♪ well, you're too hot ta stop ♪
♪ whoo, baby ♪
♪ well, you're too hot ta trot,
now, baby ♪
♪ well, you're too hot ta stop ♪
♪ whoo... ♪
Yeah, reba, it's Bob.
I was wondering
how rosette is doing.
Realized I hadn't said
a proper goodbye.
I...
I don't know if dogs think about
that sort of thing, but, uh...
Anyway, I...
Thanks again for helping out.
Bye.
Look at this.
Oh, no.
Look at this mess.
People don't have any respect.
This is gonna end up
in scat, this plastic.
I... let me pick that up.
- All right. Thank you, ranger.
- Dee Dee!
That is sticking.
- I got some oil in the car.
Dee Dee! Henry!
'Cause if that stays open,
- critters can get in there.
- Oh, yeah, critters.
What kind of critters? Huh?
- Squirrels?
- Squirrels could get in there.
Chipmunks?
- Yeah, chipmunks get in there.
- Dee Dee!
Uh, skunks.
Raccoon, you know,
little burglar.
- That's right.
- Got his own little mask on.
Yeah, with their cute little
outfit. -I think they're cute.
Uh, skunks.
Skunks. Hmm.
- Possums.
Possums.
- Definitely possums.
- Possum.
- Uh...
- Hey, possum.
Mrs. Mckinndry!
Henry?
Here! Hello?
Up here!
Hey. Whoa.
Oh.
Henry, what are you
doing up there?
No.
- No, that's not safe at all.
It's too high.
You got to come down.
Get down here.
Don't be mad,
but we skipped school.
- No shit, Henry.
It's high.
But there was a bear.
A really terrible bear.
- A bear?
- Yeah, I know.
- It was fucked!
Hey!
That's inappropriate.
Sorry for cussing,
but it attacked me and Dee Dee.
It attacked you?
- Henry, where is Dee Dee?
No, no.
Bears are
very peaceful creatures.
You must have done something
to upset it.
- Yeah, did you feed it?
- What did you do?
Nothing! Y'all need to hide!
I'm telling you,
it's not just any bear!
You have to listen to me!
Henry, where is Dee Dee?
The monster took her.
Now, I'm not gonna
tell you again, little girl.
Get down here now.
- A...
- I...
Dee Dee!
Whoa!
Peter!
- No!
- Peter!
Oh! Oh, no!
It let me go! He ran off!
- Henry, jump down.
- It's too high.
Is it gone?
Do you see it?
Yeah.
Why are you shooting at me?
Get your ass down!
This is your fault.
Right behind you. I saw it.
Stay down.
What?
Help me!
Help!
Ranger! Ranger!
Did it get you?
That asshole!
I'm gonna get him.
I'm gonna get that asshole.
I'll get help.
Where are you going?
God almighty.
Hey. What...
Where is it?
Hey!
What should I do?
Motherfucker!
Come back! Help us!
Oh, fuck!
There's something wrong with it.
Yeah, I told you there was.
Why is it acting like this?
Did you feed it cocaine?
No. But you're safe.
Bears can't climb trees.
Of course they can!
Then why are you up here?
It's okay. It's okay.
Okay.
No.
Henry, climb. Henry, go.
Climb! Climb!
You got to get higher!
- Climb.
Go, Henry!
Go!
- Henry, move!
- Go higher!
Go up!
Henry, go!
Oh, god.
Go, Henry! No!
- Whoa!
No!
Oh, god. Henry!
Oh, god.
Oh, shit.
No, no, no, no!
Get off of me! No, no!
- Get off! Get off of me!
Henry, jump! Jump down!
- Move, Henry!
It's okay. It's okay.
You're doing great.
You're almost there.
Come on, baby.
- Come on. Let's go.
Come on.
Go. Hide. Come here. Come here.
That was so messed up.
That little man
was an expert on bears
but didn't know the bear
was the cocaine bear.
Wait. What did you say?
We found cocaine,
Mrs. Mckinndry.
There was cocaine in the forest,
and the bear ate it
and then went crazy
on me and Dee Dee
and now on that guy back there.
Did you hear him scream?
He's so dead.
I'd love to not remember that.
But it kind of seems like
the thing that stays
with a man forever.
Henry, when the bear
took Dee Dee, was she...
Alive? Yeah.
It chased her that way.
We got to go. Let's go.
He get at you, too?
- Fucking beast.
- Yeah, you can say that again.
- Call an ambulance.
- I already did.
Keep him awake.
Yeah, I've been trying.
You piles of shit!
- You're the doochamps!
- Hey, that's-that's not ours.
We found it.
"It's not ours."
I'm a park ranger.
- I'm not dumb.
- I know.
They say I can't keep
my park safe,
that I'm unfit
for the big leagues.
I'd have been
at yellowstone by now
if it weren't for you shits!
- Buds.
Huh?
There's someone outside.
It's him. Get to the door.
Get to the door.
- Yeah.
Now, uh, open it
when I-I count to three.
Wait, wait.
But you're gonna shoot him?
Hell yes, I'm gonna shoot him!
He took a bite out of my ass!
What the fuck is wrong
with this guy?
Now, open it when I say so.
Now.
That's a fucking bear.
What the fuck?!
I didn't mean to. I'm sorry.
- You're sorry?
- I'm sorry.
- Where'd the bear go?
- You killed him.
Where's the bear?!
- I don't know!
- Close the door!
- Close the motherfucking door.
- Jesus Christ.
Close the door.
Oh, god. I'm sorry, bud.
Keep your mouth shut.
Check over there.
Shh.
He's up there.
I got it. I got it.
Maybe the kid can help you.
Look, I'm done
playing this game.
- What game?
- 20 questions.
Daveed's so fucking cold.
It's unbelievable.
- What did he ask so far?
- He just keeps guessing.
Like, "is it a spider?
- Is it an arrow?"
What are you, new?
Hey, start broad,
then narrow it down.
Everybody knows that.
Look, are we close
to the gazebo?
Is that one of your questions?
Oh, is it bigger
than a bread box?
No, no, no. Daveed needs to ask.
Ask him if it's bigger
than a bread box.
Is it bigger than a bread box?
- Yes.
- Whoo!
Yeah!
Is it Abraham Lincoln?
What? No.
Broad, then narrow it down, man.
You have one question left.
Dee Dee! Dee Dee!
You sure this is the way?
Pretty sure.
Dee Dee! It's okay.
It's mama.
Oh.
Thank god.
- Ew! What the heck?
It's paint. It's just red paint.
It looks a lot like blood.
How can you be sure?
I'm a nurse, Henry.
Good point.
Come on.
Oh, smart girl.
Henry, come on.
She left us a trail.
Mrs. Mckinndry,
have you ever done cocaine?
What?
Why do you ask?
Just wondering if it has
long-term side effects...
For the bear, of course,
if it just did a little bit.
Well, it could create
a habit for the bear.
What if they never want
to do it again?
Oh, then it-it should be fine.
But mama bear and papa bear
would be very angry
because drugs...
Especially cocaine...
Are very, very bad.
What if they would
never find out?
Oh, Henry.
We always find out.
Dee Dee!
♪ No more words ♪
♪ you're telling me you love me
while you're looking away ♪
♪ no more words ♪
♪ no more... ♪
Medic!
Just open it.
Yeah, open it. You think?
Can you just push?
Harder. -
- I'm doing it as hard as...
- Just let...
- All right. You go.
- Let me do it.
You go. Yeah.
Please, show me how it's done.
Go ahead, Beth.
You're strong, right?
Oh, yes, I am. Let me see.
What is that?
- See anything?
- Just, can you...
- Can you help? Can you help?
- Yeah.
What happened to feminism, huh?
Is that dead?
- Come on.
- Wait. Okay, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, fuck.
- Come on.
God, I'm trying.
- Come on, push.
I'm trying.
You said they called in
a concussion.
They did.
Jesus.
This guy's been shot.
Yeah. Obviously.
Holy shit.
It's the ranger.
- Tom.
Come here. She's got a gun.
Tom! Hello?
No, no. Put that down.
Put that down.
It's okay.
- B...
- Did you shoot that guy?
B... b...
"Buh"?
Beth?
It's okay. It's okay. Calm.
Uh...
Beth, we should go.
Shh. It's okay. It's okay.
Bear.
- Let's go.
Tom, get up!
Don't look back.
Hang on. Push.
Oh, shit.
- Sorry. Sorry.
- Come on. Come on.
Anybody else surprised by
that rain this morning?
I know I was.
Leave him!
Our next story, the weather
at the top of the hour,
but first... -Go! Drive!
More of your favorite hits
here on 103.7 Bob fm.
- Tom, get in!
- Wait! Wait!
- Wait!
- Oh, god.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Oh! Jesus, Beth,
I wasn't even on yet.
What the fuck is wrong
with that bear?
What the hell
have you got a gun for?
Hey, move! Move!
Put that away!
♪ I go out of my head ♪
♪ and I just can't
get enough... ♪
Jesus Christ!
Shoot it! Shoot it!
- Oh, shit!
Kill it!
Not the tree!
- The big fucking bear!
- Shut up!
Why is it chasing us?
♪ We slip and slide
as we fall in love... ♪
Tom, try to shut
the fucking door!
Close the fucking door,
you dumbass!
Guys, you got to stop
yelling at me!
- Oh, shit.
- Beth, speed up!
♪ I just can't get enough,
I just can't get enough ♪
♪ I just can't get enough ♪
♪ I just can't get enough... ♪
♪ You're like an angel
and you give me your love ♪
♪ and I just can't seem
to get enough of ♪
♪ I just can't get enough,
I just can't get enough ♪
♪ I just can't get enough ♪
♪ I just can't
get enough ♪
♪ I just can't get enough ♪
♪ I just can't
get enough ♪
♪ I just can't get enough ♪
♪ I just can't
get enough ♪
♪ I just can't get enough,
I just can't... ♪
I don't know
how to talk to him, you know.
Like, what-what do you say to
a kid who just lost his mommy?
My mom is the reason
I'm the man I am today.
And what a man you are.
Attacking innocent people
for no reason.
Can you not?
I'm sorry. Just continue.
Well, when my daddy died,
my mama bought me
this pet lizard.
It was the coolest little thing.
It had all these
green scales on it.
She used to call it
a tiny dinosaur.
I thought that was so awesome.
I was real bad
at connecting with people,
but I practiced
conversation starters
on that lizard every day.
And then
that's how I met rocky and Joe.
That's my team, man.
We're planning on moving
to New York City together.
Those are my buds, man.
So I should get Gabe a lizard?
Well, you know what?
Lizards are good listeners, bud,
but people...
People are good at hearing.
That's the sweetest thing
I ever heard. Thank you.
- Can we...
- It's okay.
Y'all are hugging.
It's okay.
Where the fuck is the gazebo?
Can I say something without you
getting angry with me?
I'm already angry with you.
It's gone.
What the actual...
- No! Please, please!
- Daveed, stop.
No, no, no. The kid's
messing with us, Eddie.
No, no, no! I'm not!
I'm not! I'm not!
I-I promise.
I-I don't know where it went.
It's just gone.
Okay, well,
duffel bags don't have legs.
Since you're the only one
that knew where it was,
i'm-a give you one more chance.
Where's the ba...
Put the gun down
and move away from the teenager.
Drop the weapon and step away
about five to ten paces.
All right, listen.
Just calm down, all right?
I ain't fucking around.
Just do it.
Fuck.
- You don't want to do this.
- Shut up!
I'm coming down there.
Uh...
- Uh...
Shh!
I'm just trying to...
Find a safe spot to hop down.
How did you get up there?
Well, I jumped from that tree
over there, but...
I hurt my hip a little.
I can try to catch you
if you want.
No, no!
You stay right where you are!
Let's, uh, see, uh...
Get it.
Fuck!
Well, you brought that
on yourself, kid.
Oh, yeah?
I shot my own fucking fingers?
I told you not to move.
How'd he take
those two fingers off?
They're not even
next to each other.
Fuck you!
Come out of there!
Shit! Come on out!
No fucking way!
God! Goddamn it!
You two, on your bellies.
Now! And no more moving.
Eddie! Eddie! Eddie!
Can you grab them for me?
Can I grab his fingers?
Okay. Get 'em. Get 'em.
Slow. Slow.
Easy.
Ugh, god.
All right.
Now, you get back on your belly.
I'll hold on to these.
Now, where you at?
Shit.
What?
Oh, no. The river.
Henry, look.
That's Dee Dee's sweater.
- Come on.
- So we're crossing?
We're on the right track.
I can feel it.
Mama?
Fuck.
Fuck, man.
My fucking Jersey, man.
How long are you gonna
keep us like this?
Until that guy in the gazebo
throws his weapon
into the woods.
Well, then we'll be here forever.
Hasn't Syd already
messed your life up enough?
We don't need to die
because of this.
Eddie, I got this.
Do you?
I have your fingers
in my pocket.
You're all gonna get arrested.
Drug sentences since Nixon
are fucked,
so get ready for ten to 15 years
of shitting
in front of your cellmate
and supervised shower time.
Detective, your honor, sir,
I'm not with them.
I've never even done coke.
I mean, maybe once.
Once... at a party once.
- I can't go to jail.
- You're not going to jail.
Just saying, I can't shit
in front of people.
I've never been able to shit
I like to shit in peace.
Nobody move.
It's a bear.
Yeah.
No, no.
I'm not falling
for none of your...
Oh, fuck.
Hey, y'all just stay still.
Don't move.
Just play dead.
Shh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, man. You fucked.
Eddie, can you breathe?
What the fuck?
I think that's a yes.
Can someone do something?
Maybe your boy can do something.
Can you just, like... move it?
Oh, of course.
Why didn't I think of that?
Dee Dee!
Henry, stay close.
I haven't seen paint in a while.
Oh, god.
Look.
Hello.
- Is he okay?
Help me, please.
Does he have food?
Her name was Elsa,
and she was so beautiful.
Are-are you... are you hurt?
Were you attacked?
Devil bear.
My... I'm looking
for my daughter.
She was attacked
by the devil bear.
Have you seen her?
You have?
- Was she alive?
Yes.
Please, can you just point
to where she went?
Please, can you show me?
I'm looking for her.
I haven't...
Henry!
I'll show you. Come.
It's not moving.
I think it died.
It died on top of me?
Check its pulse.
Can you, like,
feel it breathing?
I'm not sure.
Uh, hey, guy?
Detective.
Can we call a truce
so I can see
if the bear is dead?
Yeah.
Fuck.
You okay?
What do you think?
S-Still breathing.
We should go.
He'll probably be all right.
What the hell, man?
He's gonna wake up eventually.
Well, that's exactly
what I'm afraid of.
"She."
What?
The bear is a girl.
Oh, yeah.
H-How do you know that?
Because its vagina is on my ear.
Oh, shit. She's moving.
She's awake.
Oh, shit.
Well, stay back. Stay back.
Okay.
Chill out. Just chill out!
Ooh. Homes, hey, hey.
- Stay back.
What the hell?
Okay. Okay.
No, no, no, no.
Don't eat that. Don't eat that.
I will be goddamned.
Should we shoot her?
No. Let's see what kind
of effect that has on it.
What the fuck?
- No, no, no, no, no, no!
- Eddie!
Daveed, help.
What is this?
- No, no.
- Ooh! Okay, I have...
What is it doing?
I-I don't like this.
Please stop.
- Just go limp! Slide down!
- I'm limp already.
- Shoot the bear! Shoot her!
Don't shoot!
No, no. Don't shoot.
Don't shoot.
Eddie, you got to fight back,
all right?
It's-it's playing with you.
I'd stay still if I were you.
Bud, just tap out, bud.
Bud, tap out!
Eddie, please don't die
like this. Eddie, please.
Daveed!
All we've been through! Come on!
Come on, help him!
Get lower. You're not listening!
- Eddie.
Oh, my god. He's gonna die.
No!
Hey, girl.
There you go, girl.
There you go.
It's like cocaine Christmas.
Go!
Don't have to tell me twice.
Come on!
Daveed!
That bag's worth 14 million.
We had a truce, and a truce
is on god where I'm from.
Can't you see I'm trying
to help you, kid? Go!
I need that bag.
Leave it, man.
Let's just go home.
We're taking that bag
to Syd, Eddie.
Shot...
No. I didn't.
Run! Go, go!
Oh, shit!
Holy shit.
- Dad. What are you doing here?
Oh, shit.
Where's Gabe?
You didn't bring him here,
did you?
- Calm down.
He's safe at home watching TV.
What?
How long has he been alone?
You left him with me!
Do I look like
"daddy day care center" to you?
- Huh?
- The fuck happened to you?
- A lot.
- Did you get the coke?
- A little.
The bear ate most of it.
- What?
- The bear.
It fucking did cocaine.
A fucking...
A bear did cocaine, dad!
Fuck this!
Seriously,
fuck this entire journey.
Eddie, Eddie, just calm down.
Look at me. Look at me.
I'm on the hook here.
A lot of cocaine was lost
under my eye.
And the people that I deal with,
they don't care how,
just that it was.
And look at me.
They're gonna come after me,
my family
if I don't get them
every penny's worth.
You hear what I'm saying?
It's you and Gabe.
You understand?
We don't have a choice.
There's a bag
with the cop and the bear
over at the pavilion structure.
Come on.
Come on, son. Come on.
Who's there?
Easy.
Stay away.
Where's the duffel?
I gave it to the bear.
You gave it to the bear?
Yeah. The bear.
It loves coke.
Wh-which way did it go?
I'm not fucking around here.
Syd white.
Man, I've been following you
for years.
They all have.
Reba.
Oh, I always knew
you were my girl.
I got you now.
Be careful
when you cuff these guys.
They're kind of shifty.
What...
What are you doing?
- I'm sorry, Bob.
You shot him?
I told you not to hurt him.
I don't work for you.
The department trusted you.
The state of Tennessee
trusted you.
The United States of America,
it trusted you.
I know.
- I trusted you with rosette.
- I know.
Who's rosette?
The dog in my car.
You left a dog in the car?
You left my son in Saint Louis.
How is she?
She being a good girl?
Yeah. She's such a good girl.
E-Enough.
Tell me which way the bear went,
or I'm gonna kill the dog
when I come down mountain.
Oh, no, no, please,
d-don't-don't do that.
I'd vote for not
killing the dog today,
but that's just me.
Well, what do you guys say?
What's so funny?
Apex predator,
high on cocaine,
and you're going towards it.
Dead north, man.
- Yes, we will.
Dead... dead north.
Let's go.
The devil bear is in there.
You can't go in there.
Do you have kids?
We would have.
I have to go find mine.
And his name would be Texas.
- Do you have a flashlight?
- Yeah.
Here.
Thank you.
Bye, lady and little man.
Bye, you both.
Okay.
Wait. What about me?
Watch where you step.
- I got you. Stay close.
What's that?
Don't move.
Stay still, Henry.
They look like polar bears.
Henry?
Dee Dee?
- Mama!
Don't move. I'm gonna get you
out of here, okay?
No, no. Them, they're...
They're harmless. -Dee Dee!
- Mama, I just...
- Baby!
Dee Dee, you're okay.
Are you hurt?
- It's just my leg.
- Your leg?
That looks really deep.
Here. Don't touch it.
- Ow! Ow! Henry!
Let's keep you warm.
Oh, my gosh.
You found my sweater.
You smart girl.
- You left us clues.
- Yeah.
We found you.
Put that on.
- Mom, I'm so sorry.
- Oh, I love you so much.
Oh, my god.
Mom, i'm-I'm so sorry.
- I'm sorry. I just...
- It's okay.
Henry told me everything.
Everything?
You mean that
you guys did drugs?
- You told her?
No.
I had a suspicion,
and you just confirmed it.
I'm just so glad I found you
and you're okay.
- Um, what was that?
Cocaine bear's back.
- Can you walk?
- Uh, a little.
Come on. Let's go, Henry.
Go that way.
Go ahead.
It's okay. Come on.
Look. It's a way out.
It's the falls.
Oh, wow.
Henry, stay away from the ledge!
Oh, god.
This is it.
Syd, let's cut our losses.
All right? Let's just deal
with the fallout.
You saw what that bear did
to that hiker.
What is that?
- Oh, fuck!
What the fuck? What the fuck?
Come on.
Eddie.
Take this.
Fuck.
Thank you.
Goddamn bear.
Eddie, put the rest in the bag.
You got what you wanted?
Let's go.
There's-there's a lot more
out there.
We got to keep looking, understand?
We're not whole yet.
I'm leaving, Syd.
Go.
Give me the bag.
When did you all get so soft?
All got sand in your pussies.
Mom! How are we gonna
get out of here?
It's a dead end. What do we do?
Stay away from the bears.
This way.
Come on. There's an opening.
Henry, come here.
Dee Dee, get in here.
Someone's coming.
He has a gun.
No!
Come on!
The hell is this?
Whoa. Take it easy.
Take it easy.
- Dad.
- Who are you?
I'm a mom.
Syd, there's kids here.
Let's just go.
No, I'm not leaving
without that cocaine!
So somebody better bring it down
or somebody else is gonna die.
You understand?
Go.
Come on. Help him out!
- Yeah, yeah.
It's stuck.
Fuck!
Who are these guys?
We're going home.
W-We're not gonna say anything,
but we're going home.
Nobody's going anywhere!
- Dad.
- Shut up, Eddie.
- Dad!
- Shut...
Get away. Back off. Back off.
Get out of here,
you little fuckers!
- Fuck.
Get back! Get... fuckers!
- Stay away.
- Whoa.
Stay away.
Whoa. He hit the bear.
Just give 'em the bag.
Shoot the fucking bears!
- Get over here.
- Dee Dee and Henry: Whoa!
Hey, can't get a shot.
They're too close to me!
Give them the fucking coke.
They're little cubs.
The fuck's the matter with you?
Shoot the little
fucking cubs, Eddie!
Get 'em off me!
- Fuck him.
Help me out!
Ow. Eddie!
- Ow!
- No.
Coward. Daveed!
Here, catch.
I am taking
the fucking children home.
Mama!
Hell yeah, Mrs. Mckinndry.
Look around, dad.
Kids have been dragged
into this.
Get-get out of here,
you little fuckers!
People are dead.
You are no son of mine.
Hey, you!
You did this.
You're the reason
this is all happening.
And it's a good thing
he's not like you,
because you're
a piece of crap person
and a bad dad!
Who the fuck are you?
I'm Henry,
and I am so fucking tired!
Yeah, me, too.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
She's protecting the cubs.
Oh, shit!
- We need to jump.
- Wait, what?
- What? I'll be fine!
It's gonna be okay.
We're gonna be okay.
Here, here, here.
Have some coke,
you little shits.
- Get out of here!
- It's not that far, you guys.
- We're gonna be all right.
- Ready?
Mm-hmm.
Three, two, one. Jump!
- Oh, shit.
Oh, shit. We got to jump.
Let's go!
- Come on. It's okay.
Eddie. Help.
We made it.
Get the shit out of here,
you fuck!
- Oh, shit. He shot you.
Help! Help!
S-Six more days of John.
Okay.
Six more days...
I need you to know,
what I said earlier...
You're more than a drug dealer,
all right?
You're my friend.
You're my best friend.
- All right?
- Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Hey, hey, I...
I got my last question.
What?
It's 20 questions.
I got my last one.
What? All right. Sure.
Is it joanie?
It's joanie, right?
- Yeah.
How'd you guess?
You're so fucking obvious.
I just didn't want to guess it
to have you crying on me
all day.
She's a nurse!
He-he got grazed by a bullet.
He's in shock.
Put pressure on him.
I've called backup.
Her name's rosette.
She doesn't like fetch.
You should get going.
Take care of yourself.
Hi. Hi.
Rosette.
Whose dog is this?
I think it's mine.
Mine and Gabe's.
Is it on cocaine?
No.
That's a good dog.
So we just grab Gabe
and go, right?
Yeah.
I knew you'd be okay.
You're the toughest person
I know.
I think you get that
from your mom.
I think you're right.
Thanks for coming to get me.
I'm your mom. I love you.
You, too, Henry.
Hey, I'm sorry I pushed ray
on you too soon.
No. You deserve to be happy.
Henry, let's walk over here.
- Stay away from that. Come on.
I want to look.
I also don't want to look.
Ugh.
Don't look.
- Let's just cruise on by.
Oh, here come the po-po.
Hey, mom.
I want to go to Nashville
with you and ray.
Maybe we can go after
me and Henry get out of rehab.
Rehab?
We're cokeheads now.
You know?
We got the bite,
and we're about that life,
- Mrs. Mckinndry.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, you're
too grounded for rehab.
Rodney, are you getting it?
I swear to god, Carol.
Well, then zoom in.
- Is the red light on?
- No, I got it.
Oh, they're so cute.
Oh, this is gonna be good.
Wait.
Why are they looking
at us like that?
Oh.
Oh, shit.
♪ Bass ♪
♪ ooh, white ♪
♪ white ♪
♪ ooh, white lines ♪
♪ vision, dreams of passion ♪
♪ blowing through my mind ♪
♪ and all the while
I think of you ♪
♪ high price ♪
♪ a very strange reaction ♪
♪ for us to unwind ♪
♪ the more I see,
the more I do ♪
♪ something like a phenomenon ♪
♪ baby ♪
♪ telling your body
to come along ♪
♪ but white lines ♪
♪ blow away ♪
Hey.
Oh, hold up. Hold up. Hey.
♪ Rang dang diggedy
dang di-dang ♪
♪ rang dang
diggedy dang di-dang ♪
♪ rang dang diggedy
dang di-dang ♪
♪ diggedy dang di-dang,
diggedy dang di-dang ♪
♪ freeze ♪
♪ rock ♪
♪ blow ♪
♪ higher, baby ♪
♪ get higher, baby ♪
♪ get higher, baby, come on! ♪
♪ A million magic crystals ♪
♪ painted pure and white ♪
♪ a multimillion dollars ♪
♪ almost overnight ♪
♪ twice as sweet as sugar,
twice as bitter as salt ♪
♪ and if you get hooked, baby ♪
♪ it's nobody else's fault,
so don't do it... ♪
Daddy!
Is that for me?
Hey.
Yeah, what do you think?
♪ Rang dang diggedy
dang di-dang... ♪
What's it eating?
♪ Diggedy dang di-dang ♪
♪ rang dang diggedy
dang di-dang... ♪
Oh, my god.
They're weren't gonna
put 'em back on.
♪ Freeze ♪
♪ rock ♪
♪ freeze ♪
♪ and blow ♪
♪ higher, baby ♪
♪ get higher, baby ♪
♪ get higher, baby,
and don't ever come down ♪
♪ freebase. ♪
Provided by DragonHQD
Modify by Blue-Bird™